pusher.com 2017-07-08

# Privacy | Pusher

Pusher Limited (“We” or “we”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our terms of use [pusher.com/legal/aup](https://pusher.com/legal/aup) and any other documents referred to in it) (the “Terms of Service”) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting pusher.com (“our site”) you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy. Unless otherwise defined, defined terms in this Privacy Policy have the definitions given to them in the Terms of Service.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the “Act”), the data controller is Pusher Limited of 28 Scrutton Street, London, EC2A 4RP.

## Information We Collect From You

We will collect and process the following data about you:

  * **Information you give us**. This is information about you that you give us by filling in forms on our site or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise. It includes information you provide when you register to use our site, subscribe to our service, and when you report a problem with our site. The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number, financial and credit card information, VAT number and tax information.
  * **Information we collect about you from our Site or when using our Service**. When you visit our site or use our service we will automatically collect the following information: 
    * technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer or server to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform;
    * information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL), clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time), products you viewed or searched for, page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), methods used to browse away from the page, and any phone number used to call our customer service number.

## Cookies

Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our site. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them see our Cookie policy.

## Uses Made of the Information

We use information held about you in the following ways:

  * **Information you give to us**. We will use this information: 
    * to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information, products and services that you request from us;
    * to provide you with information about other goods and services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about;
    * to notify you about changes to our service;
    * to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer; and
    * we may publish feedback or support requests you send us in order to clarify or respond to your request, or to help support other users.
  * **Information we collect about you**. We will use this information: 
    * to provide our Service to you;
    * to administer our site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;
    * to improve our site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;
    * as part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secure;
    * to measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you;
    * to make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our site about goods or services that may interest you or them.

## Disclosure of Your Information

You agree that we have the right to share your personal information with:

  * any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006;
  * selected third parties including: 
    * business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you;
    * advertisers and advertising networks that require the data to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others;
    * analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our site;
    * credit reference agencies for the purpose of assessing your credit score where this is a condition of us entering into a contract with you.

We will only disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we will disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;
  * if Pusher Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets;
  * if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms of Service and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Pusher Limited, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## Where We Store Your Personal Data

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, stored and processed at, a destination outside your home country or the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside your home country or the EEA, who work for us or for one of our suppliers. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

## Your Rights

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at Pusher Limited at 28 Scrutton Street, London, EC2A 4RP or by emailing us at [support@pusher.com](mailto:support@pusher.com) with the subject line “Unsubscribe”.

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

## Access to Information

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request will be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

## Important Notice - Information Uploaded or Transmitted as Part of the Service

You or end users of your Application may upload and transmit Content as part of the Service that contains personal data relating to you or other individuals. We do not view, store or control such Content and simply transmit the Content on behalf or you or the owner of the Application in accordance with our Terms of Service. You expressly acknowledge that you or the person uploading the Content (as applicable) retain sole responsibility for the Content and for obtaining all relevant consents, from the individual to which any personal data contained within the Content relates, to the processing of that personal data as part of the Service, and that such personal data is not covered by this Privacy Policy. Content may be processed in the EEA or in the US, depending on the location of the server cluster the operator of the Application has elected as part of the Service. It is the responsibility of the operator of each Application to ensure that it has a suitable privacy policy in place to cover the transmission and processing of the Content and any personal data that it contains.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

Any changes we make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to Pusher Limited at 28 Scrutton Street, London, EC2A 4RP or [support@pusher.com](mailto:support@pusher.com).
